<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://nonzero.day/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://nonzero.day/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-10-03T00:56:38-07:00</updated><id>https://nonzero.day/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Non-Zero Day</title><subtitle>Consistent chain of non-zero day.</subtitle><author><name>Non-Zero Day</name><email>chesterhow@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">Continue</title><link href="https://nonzero.day/2025-10-03/continue" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Continue" /><published>2025-10-03T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2025-10-03T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>https://nonzero.day/2025-10-03/continue</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://nonzero.day/2025-10-03/continue"><![CDATA[<p>The original theme that I was using was very limited, at which point I found out, only displayed <!--more-->one post per day. Although I posted a couple, only the oldest would display for that day. Good I found out early! 😂</p>

<p>I have learned a lot since I started doing <stong>non-zero day&lt;/strong&gt;. I view time more valuable and see time as finite. I never view my time that way before. Now that I try to squeeze everything that I can in one say, I seem to have so much more leftover to do and have to wait for the next day.  I am still working on sleeping at 10:00 P.M. One of my to dos, is to sleep more hours, as based on studies that I have read, listened to, uninterrupted sleep is required for a healthy life.  I have been sleeping three to four hours for most of my life, and at times even less. <strong>But</strong>, did I use all the waking time wisely?  I would say eighty-five percent of the time I wasted doing non-essential things, like watching shows that did not improve my life.  Knowing what I know now, and I had all that time and optimized those days that I wasted, I truly believe I would have a much more different life, <strong>IF</strong> I implemented then what I am implementing now.</stong></p>

<p>In closing I would just like to provide a two quotes:</p>

<blockquote>"You don't have to be great to start, but you have to start to be great." -Zig Ziglar 1985</blockquote>

<blockquote>"A year from now you may wish you had started today." -Karen Lamb</blockquote>]]></content><author><name>Non-Zero Day</name></author><category term="Start" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original theme that I was using was very limited, at which point I found out, only displayed]]></summary></entry></feed>